

TRUONG Q. QUOC TU

Java Developer

- 18/03/1996
- Male
- +84 98 1875370
- ☐ rimtruong@gmail.com
- A Ho Chi Minh city
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/t utqq/

SKILLS

Java

JavaScript



••••



Maven



MongoDB



PostgresDB



JQuery

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Forward-thinking Software Engineer with a background in working productively in dynamic environments. Fluent in **Java** programming languages with more than **3 years** of experience in a fast-paced technology company. Proud team player focused on achieving project objectives with speed and accuracy.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

08/2022 - PRESENT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | FPT Software

- B2CAMS_22 (Jul 2022 Aug 2022)
- Carepak (Aug 2022 Nov 2022)

01/2022 - 08/2022

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | Viettel IDC

- Multi- CDN (Dec 2021 - Jul 2022)

09/2019 - 12/2021

JAVA DEVELOPER | iNet Solutions Corp.

- Data Migration (migration from Postgres to MongoDB)
- OneGate (maintenance and develop new features)
- Expway (maintenance and develop new features)
- ESB (Jan 2020 Jun 2020)
- Portal (Sep 2019 Jan 2020)

CERTIFICATIONS

2022

IBM FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER SPECIALIZATION

2022

CLOUD APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATIONS SPECIALIZATION

2019

JAVA PROGRAMMER CERTIFICATE ISSUED BY THE CENTER FOR INFORMATICS - UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY, HO CHI MINH CITY.

HONORS & AWARDS

2020

EXCELLENT EMPLOYEE OF THE YEAR INET SOLUTIONS CORP.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

NO DEGREE : HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORT | Major: networking and communication system(IT)

